There's one more object oriented topic to cover in this lesson, inheritance.
这节课还要介绍一个面向对象概念 继承
I think inheritance is easier to understand using
举个实际的例子 这样更容易理解这一概念
a real world object like the shirt example from earlier in the lesson.
例如之前的衬衫例子
The shirt had four attributes,
Shirt 有四个属性
a color, size, style, and price.
color size style 和 price
The shirt also had two methods.
Shirt 还有两个方法
A method to change the price,
分别是更改价格方法
and a method for calculating a discounted price.
和计算折扣价方法
As the store expands,
随着商店的扩张
it might stock other types of clothing like pants, socks, and dresses.
可能会出售其他服饰 例如裤子 袜子和裙子
These garments have a few attributes and methods in common with the shirt object.
这些服饰和衬衫对象具有一些相同的属性和方法
They probably all have a color, size, style,
它们可能都具有 color size style 和 price
and price and, they could all use functions to change the price and calculate a discount.
可能都会使用函数来更改价格和计算折扣价
Why code separate classes for each new garment when they all have so much in common?
如果它们都具有很多共同点 为何要分别编写不同的类呢？
Instead, you could code apparent clothing class,
你可以编写一个 Clothing 父类
and then the pants, socks,
然后 Pants Socks
dresses, and shirts classes,
Dresses 和 Shirts 类
could inherit the attributes and methods of the clothing class.
等就可以继承 Clothing 类的属性和方法
This looks like a family tree where clothing is the parent,
看起来就像一个族谱 Clothing 是父母
and pants, socks, dresses,
Pants Socks Dresses 和 Shirts
and shirts, are the children.
是子女
One benefit is that,
这么做的一个优势是
as you add more clothing types like blouses,
当你添加衬衫等更多服饰类型时
you can easily add a new class that inherits from the clothing class as well.
你可以轻松地添加一个继承 Clothing 类属性的新类
What if you wanted to add a new attribute like
如果你想添加新的属性呢
material to represent if the garment is made of cotton,
例如 material 表示服饰材质
nylon, or some other fabric?
是棉质 尼龙或其他材质
Now, all you have to do is,
你只需
add a material attribute to the clothing class,
向 Clothing 类添加 material 属性
and all the children classes automatically inherit the new attribute.
所有子类将自动继承新属性
Your code becomes more efficient to write and maintain.
这样代码编写和维护起来更高效
Next, I'll go through the Python syntax, for inheritance.
接下来我将介绍继承的 Python 语法
Then, you'll add inheritance to the Gaussian class.
然后你将向 Gaussian 类添加继承代码